Guide to the BOMB Magazine Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: BOMB Publications, 1981-2005
  - Subseries II.1: Issues, 1981-2005
    - Issue 103, Spring 2008 and Summary
      - Interview: Steve DiBenedetto by David Humphrey (Box 136)
      - Interview Zachary Lazar by Christopher Sorrentino (Box 136)
      - Interview: Philip Seymour Hoffman by June Stein (Box 136)
      - Interview: Raja Alem by Tom McDonough (Box 136)
      - Interview: Joseph Bartscherer by James Welling (Box 136)
      - Interview: Tav Falco by Erik Morse (Box 136)
      - Interview: Adam Zameenzad by Indran Amirthanayagam (Box 136)
      - First Proof: “Herb and Rosalie Swanson at the Cocoanut Grove” by Peter Orner (Box 136)
      - Poems by Bradford Gray Telford (Box 136)
      - Excerpt from Trauma by Patrick McGrath (Box 136)
      - Poems by Elena Georgiou (Box 136)
      - “Prayer for Some of What Was Lost” by Paul Maliszewski (Box 136)
      - “And It’s Hard for Her to Imagine It Now” by Hannah Pittard (Box 136)
      - Issue 103, Spring 2008 (Box 137)
      - “Yes” by Linda Bamber (Box 137)
      - An Excerpt from Alice Invents a Play and Always Wins, “Afterword” by Nick Flynn (Box 137)
      - First Proof Redesign (Box 137)
      - An Excerpt from The Codeswitchers, “Annika Ona: An Introduction” (Box 137)
      - Phone Messages for Betsy Sussler (Box 137)
      - The Random House, Inc. Creative Writing Contest for NYC Public High School Seniors (Box 137)
      - Paul Graham’s A Shimmer of Possibility by Tod Papageorge (Box 137)
    - Issue 104, Summer 2008
      - Front Matter and Layouts (Box 137)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 137)
      - Deborah Grant (Box 137)
      - Michael Goldberg In Memoriam (Box 137)
      - Artists on Artists: Michèle Gerber Klein on Tristan Perich (Box 137)
      - Artists on Artists: B. Wurtz on Charles Goldman (Box 137)
      - Artists on Artists: Whitfield Lovell on Leslie Hewitt (Box 137)
      - Catherine Sullivan and Meg Stuart in Conversation (Box 137)
      - Interview: Will Eno by Joe Sola (Box 137)
      - Interview: Kalup Linzy by Nick Stillman (Box 137)
      - “Boredoms” (Interview: Yamatsuka Eye by Hisham Bharoocha) (Box 137)
      - Interview: Dara Birnbaum by Karen Kelley and Barbara Schroeder (Box 137)
      - Interview: James Timberlake by Deven Golden (Box 137)
      - Interview” Peter Saul by Saul Ostrow (Box 137)
      - Issue 104, Summer 2008 (Box 138)
      - Interview: Mike David by Lucy Raven (Box 138)
      - Poems by Sally Dawidoff (Box 138)
      - Marjorie Welish (Box 138)
      - The Shanghai Gesture by Gary Indiana (Box 138)
      - Poems by Vincent Katz (Box 138)
      - Short Stories by Christoph Keller and Heinrich Kuhn (Box 138)
      - “Patriots” by Patrick Dacey (Box 138)
      - “House” by Karen Thompson (Fiction Prize Winner) (Box 138)
      - “Some Poblems, Cha-cha-cha” by Fiona Maazel (Box 138)
      - Saltwork by Tom Healy (Box 138)
      - First Proof and Layouts (Box 138)
    - Issue 105, Fall 2008
      - Subscription Cards (Holly’s Design) and Contributor Notes (Box 138)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 138)
      - Holly Zausner (Box 138)
      - Artists on Artists: Roberto Juarez on Robert Brinker (Box 138)
      - Artists on Artists: Kathryn Andrews on Chris Lipomi (Box 138)
      - Interview: Claire Fontaine by Anthony Huberman (Box 138)
      - Interview: John Giorno by Marcus Boon (Box 138)
      - Interview: Richard Maxwell by John Kelsey (Box 138)
      - Rachel Harrison and Nayland Blake in Conversation (Box 138)
      - Interview: Peter Cole by Ben Lerner (Box 138)
      - “Art Doesn’t Come From Ability” (Interview: Roman Singer by Armin Senser, trs. Claudia Steinberg) (Box 138)
      - Interview: Gus Van Sant by Kelly Reichardt (Box 138)
      - Interview: Alan Vega by Matt McCauley and Brain McPeck (Box 138)
      - Downtown Body Postmortem, a Collection of Memories, edited by Ward Shelley (Box 138)
      - Issue 105, Fall 2008 (Box 139)
      - First Proof: Paul Bloodgood (Box 139)
      - “The Poet’s Ghost” by Carmen Boullosa, trs. by Samantha Schnee (Box 139)
      - “Captain, Sir, we have plenty of coffee!” by Dubravka Ugresic (Box 139)
      - Poems by Ted Mathys (Box 139)
      - Patricia Cronin Portfolio (Box 139)
      - An Excerpt from Where the Line Bleeds by Jenny Ward (Box 139)
      - An Excerpt from You Are Here, “First Friday in June ” by Donald Breckenridge (Box 139)
      - Layouts (Box 139)
      - Sketch for the Downtown Timeline Project Framework (Box 139)
    - Issue 106, Winter 2009
      - Alejandro Cesarco by Nicolás Guagnini (Box 139)
      - Artists on Artists: Andrew Moszynski on Fernanda Laguna (Box 139)
      - Artists on Artists: Emma Wilcox on Sebastian Patane Masueli (Box 139)
      - Javier Téllez and Cristóbal Lehyt in Conversation (Box 139)
      - Interview: Jorge Macchi by Edgardo Rudnitzky (Box 139)
      - Interview: Smiljan Radic by Jose Castillo (Box 139)
      - Interview: Lucrecia Martel by Haden Guest (Box 139)
      - Nicanor Parra by Raúl Zurita, trs. Anna Deeny (Box 139)
      - Interview: Guillermo Kuitca by Matias Duville, trs. Margaret Carson (Box 139)
      - Interview: Josefina Guilisasti by Yoshua Okon (Box 139)
      - Interview: César Aira by María Moreno, trs. Philip Penix-Tadsen (Box 139)
      - Interview: Cristina Peri Rossi by Carmen Boullosa (Box 139)
      - Interview: Adrián Dárgelos of the Babasónicos by Laureana Toledo (Box 139)
      - “Venice Without Me (Piazza San Marco)” by María Moreno, trs. by Jessica Ernst (Box 139)
      - Poetry Bomb 106 (Box 139)
      - An Excerpt from Mis Dos Mundos by Sergio Chejfec (Box 139)
      - Short Stories by Lina Meruane, trs. Bernadette Walker and Ronald Christ (Box 139)
      - “Ut pictura poesis” by Roberto Echavarren (Box 139)
      - Issue 106, Winter 2009 (Box 140)
      - “Mi vida como un hombre: un diario intimo” by Alan Pauls, trs. Nick Caistor (Box 140)
      - Vincente Grondona (Box 140)
      - Layouts (Box 140)
      - Layouts (2) (Box 140)
      - Layouts (3) (Box 140)
      - Layouts (4) (Box 140)
    - Issue 107, Spring 2009
      - Issue 107, Spring 2009 and Summary (Box 140)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 140)
      - Charcoal Paintings by Joyce Pensato (Box 140)
      - Visual Art by Charles Mary Kubricht (Box 140)
      - Fiction for Driving: “Everything You See Is Real” by Ben Ehrenreich (Box 140)
      - Short Stories by Michael Martone (Box 140)
      - 107 Audio (Box 140)
      - Interview: Pauline Oliveros by Cory Arcangel (Box 140)
      - Interview: Roxy Paine by Billie Tsien and Tod Williams (Box 140)
      - Interview: Jacqueline Humphries by Cecily Brown (Box 140)
      - Interview: The Yes Men by Steve Lambert (Box 140)
      - Interview: Eric Kraft by Andrei Codrescu (Box 140)
      - Interview: Matthew Buckingham by Josiah McElheny (Box 140)
      - BOMB Specific: David Clarkson (Box 140)
      - Artists on Artists: Kara Walker on Mickalene Thomas (Box 140)
      - Interview: Mary Gaitskill by Matthew Sharpe (Box 140)
      - Short Stories by Sally Anne Clegg (Box 140)
      - Artists on Artists: Sanford Biggers on Rashid Johnson (Box 140)
      - Interviews: Adam Bartos by AM Homes (Box 140)
      - Issue 107, Spring 2009 (Box 141)
      - “Traveling Fools” by Ana Menéndez (Box 141)
      - Poems by Laura Mullen and Rusty Morrison (Box 141)
      - Emily Jacir (Box 141)
      - First Proof (Box 141)
    - Issue 108, Summer 2009
      - Front Matter (Box 141)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 141)
      - Interview: Carrie Mae Weems by Dawoud Bey (Box 141)
      - Interview: Harry Dodge and Stanya Kahn by Mike Smith (Box 141)
      - Interview: Kelly Copper and Pavol Liska (Nature Theater of Oklahoma) by Young Jean Lee (Box 141)
      - Interview: Jacques Roubaud by Marcella Durand (Box 141)
      - Interview: Bill Callahan by Jon Raymond (Box 141)
      - Interview: Nam Le by Charles D’Ambrosio (Box 141)
      - Interview: Guy Maddin by Isabella Rossellini (Box 141)
      - Interview: Joe Bradley by Dike Blair (Box 141)
      - Artists on Artists: Rob Fisher on Michael Combs (Box 141)
      - Artists on Artists: George Negroponte on Dan Wolgers (Box 141)
      - Artists on Artists: Adam Pendleton on Xaviera Simmons (Box 141)
      - Fiction for Driving: “The Bar on Tompkins Square Park: Self Portrait with Blue Horse” by Frederic Tuten (Box 141)
      - “Wayward Sleep” by Tara Goedjen (Box 141)
      - Short Stories from Let the Great World Spin by Colum McCann (Box 141)
      - Visual Art by Adam Simon and Matthew Sharpe (Box 141)
      - Poetry BOMB 108 (Box 141)
    - Issue 109, Fall 2009
      - Layouts (Box 141)
      - Interview: Joel Shapiro by Michèle Gerber Klein (Box 141)
      - Interview: Rebecca Solnit by Astra Taylor (Box 141)
      - Issue 109, Fall 2009 (Box 142)
      - Interview: Karole Armitage by Lukas Ligeti (Box 142)
      - Interview: Allen Ruppersberg by Cheryl Donegan (Box 142)
      - Interview: Cherien Dabis by June Stein (Box 142)
      - Interview: Thomas Bradshaw by Margo Jefferson (Box 142)
      - Interview: Lydia Peelle by Gillian Welch (Box 142)
      - Artists on Artists: Diana al-Hadid on Tala Madani (Box 142)
      - Artists on Artists: James Siena on Dan Schmidt (Box 142)
      - Micachu by Anni Rossi (Box 142)
      - First Proof Summer 2009 (Box 142)
      - “Scoring Warhol’s Screen Tests” by Dean Wareham (Box 142)
      - Interview: So Yong Kim by Ryan Fleck and Bradley Rust Gray (Box 142)
      - Interview: Jennifer Allora and Guillermo Calzadilla by Carlos Motta (Box 142)
      - Visual Art by RH Quaytman (Box 142)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 142)
      - Interview: Eileen Quinland by Walead Beshty (Box 142)
      - Prints of Potential Covers (Box 142)
      - Visual Art by Valerie Belin (Box 142)
    - Issue 110, Winter 2010
      - Americas Issue: Venezuela/Colombia/Peru (Box 143)
      - Statement of Ownership Controversy (Box 143)
      - First Proof Winter 2010 (Box 143)
      - Artists on Artists: José Ruiz on Esperanza May obre (Box 143)
      - Lugar a Dudas by José Tomás Giraldo (Box 143)
      - Nascimiento/Lovera by Gabriela Rangel M (Box 143)
      - Interview: Antonieta Sosa by Fanklin Fernández (Box 143)
      - Alvaro Barrios (Box 143)
      - Interview: Antonio Caro by Víctor Manuel Rodríguez (Box 143)
      - Interview: Evelio Rosero by Antonio Ungar, trs. Anne McLean (Box 143)
      - Sergio Fajardo and Giancarlo Mazzanti in Conversation, trs. Phillip Penix-Tadsen (Box 143)
      - Interview: Ana Teresa Torres by Carmen Boullosa (Box 143)
      - Interview: Dulce Gómez by Rafael Castillo Zapata (Box 143)
      - Interview: Carlos Cruz-Diez by Estrellita Brodsky (Box 143)
      - Juan Gabriel Vásquez by Silvana Paternostro (Box 143)
      - Interview: Mario Galeando Toro by Marc Nasdor (Box 143)
      - Interview: Javier Téllez by Pedro Reyes, trs. Jen Hofer (Box 143)
    - Issue 111, Spring 2010
      - Interview: Mike Glier by Roberto Juarez (Box 143)
      - Interview: Harvey Shapiro by Maggie Paley (Box 143)
      - Interview: Amanda Ross-Ho by Elad Lassry (Box 143)
      - Web Spread (Box 143)
      - Issue 111, Spring 2010 (Box 144)
      - First Proof (Box 144)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 144)
      - Artists on Artists: Jimbo Blachly on Joanna Malinowska (Box 144)
      - Artists on Artists: Josef Strau on Alex Hubbard (Box 144)
      - BOMB Specific 111 (Box 144)
      - Artists on Artists: Minna Proctor by Sharon Harper (Box 144)
      - Interview: TJ Wilcox by Anne Collier (Box 144)
      - Interview: Carlos Reygadas by José Castillo, trs. Camino Detorrela (Box 144)
      - Interview: David Sylvian by Keith Rowe (Box 144)
      - Interview: Sam Lipsyte by Chris Sorrentino (Box 144)
      - Interview: Charles Berstien by Jay Sanders (Box 144)
      - Interview: Edgar Arceneaux by Charles Gaines and Rick Lowe (Box 144)
      - Interview: Patricia Clarkson by Howard Altmann (Box 144)
      - Interview: Guy Ben-Ner by Thom Donovan (Box 144)
    - Issue 112, Summer 2010
      - Proof of Issue 112, Summer 2010 (Box 144)
      - Interview: Joan Jonas by Karin Schneider (Box 144)
      - Interview: Dan Asher by Ben Berlow (Box 144)
      - Interview: Alain Mabanckou by Binyavanga Wainaina (Box 144)
      - Interview: Cynthia Hopkins by Annie-B Parson (Box 144)
      - Issue 112, Summer 2010 (Box 145)
      - First Proof (Box 145)
      - Steven’s Pictures (Box 145)
      - Front Pages (Box 145)
      - Interview: Jennifer Egan by Heidi Julavits (Box 145)
      - Interview: Elizabeth Streb by AM Homes (Box 145)
      - Interview: Jessica Jackson Horodner (Box 145)
      - Interview: Edward Droste by Rick Moody (Box 145)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 145)
      - “Futurefarmers” by David van der Leer (Box 145)
      - Artists on Artists: Ed Halter on Andrew Lampert (Box 145)
      - Artists on Artists: Stephen Westfall on Cordy Ryman (Box 145)
      - BOMB Specific Summer 2010 Fiona Banner (Box 145)
      - Interview: Joan Jonas by Karin Schneider (2) (Box 145)
    - Issue 113, Fall 2010
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 145)
      - Curtis Mitchell (Visual Art and Miscellaneous Articles) (Box 145)
      - BOMB Specific (Box 145)
      - Artists on Artists (Box 145)
      - Interview: Mika Rottenberg by Judy Hudson (Box 145)
      - Interview: Thomas Hirschhorn by Abraham Cruzvillegas (Box 145)
      - Interview: David Toop by Keith Connolly (Box 145)
      - Interview: Adam Philips by Sameer Padania (Box 145)
      - Interview: Fred Tomaselli by David Shields (Box 145)
      - Interview: Charlie Smith by John Reed (Box 145)
      - Issue 113, Fall 2010 (Box 146)
      - Interview: Charlie Smith by John Reed (Box 146)
      - Interview: Charline Von Heyl by Shirley Kaneda (Box 146)
      - Interview: Jan Lauwers by Elizabeth LeCompte (Box 146)
      - First Proof
    - Issue 114, Winter 2011
      - BOMB 114 (Digital), Summary, and Note from Ben Ristow (Box 146)
      - The Leaves of Fate by George Robert Minkoff (Box 146)
      - Interview: Kevin Martin, aka The Bug, by Jace Clayton (Box 146)
      - Interview: Rochelle Feinstein by Justin Lieberman (Box 146)
      - Interview: Sarah Michelson by Ralph Lemon (Box 146)
      - Artists on Artists (Box 146)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 146)
      - Interview: Adam Pendleton by Thom Donavan (Box 146)
      - Interview: Rae Armantrout by Ben Lerner (Box 146)
      - Interview: Gladys Nilsson and James Nutt by Richard Hull (Box 146)
      - Interview: Tristan Garcia by Sandra Laugier, trs. Nicholas Elliott (Box 146)
      - Issue 114, Winter 2011 (Box 147)
      - BOMB 114 Corrections in Layout (Box 147)
      - Interview: Apichatpong Weerasethakul by Lawrence Chua (Box 147)
      - Front Matter (Box 147)
      - Corrections for 114 (Box 147)
      - First Proof BOMB 114 (Box 147)
    - Issue 115, Spring 2011
      - Issue 115, Spring 2011 (Digital) (Box 147)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 147)
      - Artists on Artists (Box 147)
      - Katharina Grosse (Box 147)
      - Interview: Jim Shepard by Christie Hodge (Box 147)
      - Interview: Joe Fyfe by Josh Blackwell (Box 147)
      - Interview: Sebastian Silva by Christian Viveros-Faunes (Box 147)
      - Interview: Luis Camnitzer by Alejandro Cesarco (Box 147)
      - Interview: Sibyl Kempson by Kristen Kosmas (Box 147)
      - Interview: Robert Wyatt by Shadia Mansour (Box 147)
      - Interview: Thomas Pletzinger by Sufjan Stevens, Intro by Sabine Russ (Box 147)
      - Issue 155 Draft (Box 147)
      - Copy Edits (Box 147)
      - Front Matter and Changes to the Entered (Box 147)
      - Issue 115, Spring 2011 (Box 148)
      - Artists on Artists (Box 148)
      - Huma Bhabha (Box 148)
      - First Proof 115 (Box 148)
      - Comic Session Issue (Box 148)
      - Interview: Deb Kass (Box 148)
      - Erik Moskowitz and Amanda Trager: Cloud Cuckoo Land (Box 148)
    - Issue 116, Summer 2011
      - Artists on Artists (Box 148)
      - BOMB Specific (Box 148)
      - Changes to Enter (Box 148)
      - Paul Dickerson (Box 148)
      - Correction to 114 (Apichatpong Interview) (Box 148)
      - Interview: Francis Alÿs by Carla Faesler, trs. Camino Detorrela (Box 148)
      - Interview: Natalia Almada by Chris Chang (Box 148)
      - Interview: Joanna Newsom by Roy Harper (Box 148)
      - Interview: Binyavanga Wainaina by Rob Spillman (Box 148)
      - Siri Hustvedt and Simon Van Booy in Conversation (Box 148)
      - The Wick (Box 148)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 148)
      - First Proof (Box 148)
      - Interview: Cauleen Smith by Leslie Hewitt (Box 148)
      - Interview: Scott Shepard by Richard Maxwell (Box 148)
      - Artists on Artists: Steve DiBenedetto on Michael Williams116, Summer 2011 (Box 148)
      - Interview: Mickalene Thomas by Sean Landers (Box 148)
    - Issue 117, Fall 2011
      - (On top) 117 Proofs (Box 148)
      - 117 Proofs (Box 148)
      - Artists on Artists (Box 148)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 148)
      - Front Matter (Box 148)
      - Interview: Clifford Owens by Nick Stillman (Box 148)
      - First Proof (Box 148)
      - BOMB Specific (Box 148)
      - Interview: Peter Eisenman by Carlos Brillembourg (Box 148)
      - Interview: Lisa Yuskavage by Mónica de la Torre (Box 148)
      - Interview: Neil Hagerty by Keith Connolly (Box 148)
      - Sanford Biggers by Terry Adkins (Box 148)
      - Interview: Eve Sussman by Matvej Yankelevich (Box 150)
      - Interview: Kenneth Goldsmith by Marcus Boon (Box 150)
      - Interview: Geoff Dyer by Jonathan Lethem (Box 150)
      - BOMB Issues 90-117, 2005-2011 (Box 150)
    - BOMB Live! (Box 151)
      - At the New School -- Winter 2002 (Box 151)
      - Glenn Ligon/Thelma Golden and Betsy Sussler (Box 151)
      - Peter Cole and Edward Hirsch (Box 151)
      - Jonathan Lethem (Box 151)
      - Young Jean Lee (Box 151)
      - Judy Pfaff (2008) (Box 151)
      - Ned Smyth/Keith Sonnier (Box 151)
      - Ned Smyth/Keith Sonnier (2) (Box 151)
      - Ned Smyth/Keith Sonnier, Miscellaneous Notes (Box 151)
      - Matthew Coolidge/Deborah Gans (Box 151)
      - Sharon Hayes/Lawrence Weiner (Box 151)
      - Rackstraw Downes/Philip Lopate, November 2002 (Box 151)
    - BOMB Web Exclusive 2007-2011
      - Archive Inventory 2007 (Box 151)
      - Interview: Rhys Chatham by Alan Licht (Box 151)
      - Interivew: Silvana Paternostro and Francisco Goldman (Box 151)
      - Interivew: Coco Robicheaux by Ned Sublette (Box 151)
      - Daniel Alarcón, Alex Espinoza, and Gabriela Juaregui in Conversation (Box 151)
      - Interview: Nathan Englander by Rivka Galchen (Box 151)
      - Charles Simic and Tomaz Salamun (Box 151)
      - Interview: Alexsandar Hemon by Deborah Baker (Box 151)
      - 2009 Marker (Box 151)
      - Archive Inventory 2009 (Box 151)
      - Interview: Mitch Epstein by Richard B. Woodward (Box 151)
      - Interview: Rona Pondick by Shirley Kaneda (Box 151)
      - Interview: Ann Lauterbach by John Reed (Box 151)
      - David Korins and Oskar Eustis in Conversation (Box 151)
      - Interview: Tristan Perich by Nick Hallet (Box 151)
      - Francisco Suniaga and Federico Vegas in Conversation (Box 151)
      - Interview: Margaret de Wys by Roberta Louis (Box 151)
      - Interview: Trevor Winkfield by Maggie Paley (Box 151)
      - Interview: Josephine Meckseper by Flavin Judd (Box 151)
      - Interview: Shara Worden by Tim Fite (Box 151)
      - 2010 Marker (Box 152)
      - Web Exclusives 2010-2011 (Box 152)
      - Interview: Tan Lin by Katherine Elaine Sanders (Box 152)
      - Interview: Jace Clayton by Alan Gilbert (Box 152)
      - Interview: Deborah Kass by Irving Sandler (Box 152)
      - Interview: Joe Scanlan by Jeremy Sigler (Box 152)
      - Interview: Jacques Coursil by Jason Weiss (Box 152)
      - Interview: Ralph Bakshi by Morgan Miller (Box 152)
      - Interview: Brain Ulrich by Lynn Saville (Box 152)
      - Interview: Arlene Shechet by Jane Dickson (Box 152)
      - Interview: Adina Hoffman by Deborah Baker (Box 152)
      - Interview: Bette Gordon by Evangeline Morphos (Box 152)
      - 2011 Marker (Box 152)
      - Interview: Maurizio Cattelan by Michèle Gerber Klein (Box 152)
      - Interview: Michael Counts by John Zorn (Box 152)
      - Interview: Martha Wilson by Brian Wheeler (Box 152)
      - Interview: Hans Magnus Enzensberger by Tracy K. Smith (Box 152)
      - “Correspondence” Marker (Box 152)
      - Recent Work BOMB Live (Box 152)
    - Unpublished Files
      - A Conversation Among Gerardo Mosquera, Francis Alÿs, Rafael Ortega, and Cuauhtémoc Medina (Box 153)
      - Angela Hernandez (Box 153)
      - Ani diFranco (Box 153)
      - Lover Boy -- Kevin Bacon (Box 153)
      - Simon Starling (Box 153)
      - Olive Senior (Box 153)
      - Sylvia Plachy (Box 153)
      - Gyorgy Ligeti (Box 153)
      - Artists on Artists: Ellen Harvey (Box 153)
      - Correspondence with Publishers (Box 153)
      - Karole Armitage (Box 153)
      - 2006 Fall (Box 153)
      - Gregory Rabassa (Box 153)
      - Interview: David Sinister by Adam Kleinman (Box 153)
      - John Maeda by Leanne Jouin (Box 153)
      - Interview: Oonya Kempadoo by Harald Leusmann (Box 153)
      - Nameless Interviews (Box 153)
      - Americas Folder Research (Box 153)
      - Stan Douglas (Box 153)
      - Jean Jacques Schuhl (Box 153)
      - Artists on Artists Research Miscellaneous (Box 153)
      - Rose Lee Goldberg (Box 153)
      - PR Only (Box 153)
      - John Kalymnios for AonA by Roberto Juarez 2006-07 (Box 153)
      - Teddy Cruz by Paul Ramirez Jonas (Box 153)
      - Thelma Golden (Box 153)
      - Jessica Stockholder
  - Subseries II.2: Monographs, 1991-1998
    The books are compilations of interviews based upon a specific theme, Art, Fiction and Poetry, and Theater and Film. Editor-in-Chief Betsy Sussler edited the interviews with the assistance of Suzan Sherman and Rone Shavers. Within this series is printed material, in the form of press releases, invitations to book launches, and tickets, as well as correspondence, artist forms, and financial records. Also included, in both paper and digital formats, are manuscript drafts, proofs with accompanying corrections, photographs, and advertising layouts.
    Speak Art! Interviews:
    Dave Hickey by Saul Ostrow, Eric Fischl by A.M. Homes, Roni Horn by Mimi Thompson, Robert Gober by Craig Gholson, Adam Fuss by Ross Bleckner, Larry Sultan by Catherine Liu, Richard Serra by David Seidner, Sue Williams by David Seidner and Nancy Spero, Ross Bleckner by Aimee Rankin, Vito Acconci by Richard Prince, Kiki Smith by Chuck Close, and Lawrence Weiner by Marjorie Welish
    Speak Fiction and Poetry! Interviews:
    Michael Ondaatje by Willem Dafoe, John Edgar Wideman by Caryl Phillips, Lucie Brock-Broido by Carole Maso, Russell Banks by Pinkney Benedict, Walter Mosley by Thulani Davis, Jeanette Winterson by Catherine Bush, James Merrill by Tom Bolt, bell hooks by Lawrence Chua, Francine Prose by Deborah Eisenberg, Peter Carey by Robert Polito, Paul Auster by Joseph Mallia, Tobias Wolff by A.M. Homes, Caryl Phillips by Graham Swift, Bradford Morrow by Jim Lewis, Melanie Rae Thon by Caryl Phillips, and Graham Swift by Patrick McGrath.
    Speak Theater and Film! Interviews:
    Paula Vogel by Mary-Louise Parker, Mike Figgis by Bette Gordon, Arthur Miller by Ron Rifkin, George C. Wolfe by bell hooks, Elizabeth LeCompte by Linda Yablonsky, Anna Deavere Smith by Thulani Davis, Ron Vawter by Jessica Hagedorn, Edward Albee by Craig Lucas, Lee Breuer by Michael Goldberg, Suzan-Lori Parks by Han Ong, Mike Leigh by Bette Gordon, Richard Greenberg by Craig Gholson, Frances McDormand by Willem Dafoe, and Liz Diamond by Marc Robinson.
    - General, 1991 (Box 30)
    - Speak Art!, 1997-1998
      - Benefit Party--General (Box 57)
      - Contracts (Box 61, 70)
      - Correspondence (Box 61, 70)